A Guide to the Papers of Michael J. Stolee, 1964 to 2009
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- School Desegregation Cases
  - Michigan 1974 to 1999.
    - Court Documents – United States District Court for the Western District of Michigan Southern Division 1980 to 1999
      - Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos November 28, 1988 – May 2, 1989 (Box-folder 5:26)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos May 22, 1989 (Box-folder 5:27)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee, August 31, 1989 (Box-folder 5:28)
      - Chapter I Funds September 9, 1989 (Box-folder 5:29)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos September 28, 1989 (Box-folder 5:30)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee February 22, 1989 – December 31, 1989 (Box-folder 5:31)
      - Order – Eau Claire Motion Moot January 18, 1990 (Box-folder 5:32)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos April 27, 1990 (Box-folder 5:33)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos July 5, 1990 (Box-folder 5:34)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee April 21, 1990 – December 31, 1990 (Box-folder 5:35)
      - Order -- Regarding Chapter I Funds August 16, 1990 (Box-folder 5:36)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos January 8, 1991 (Box-folder 5:37)
      - Order -- Status Conference July 18, 1991 (Box-folder 5:38)
      - Order – Continuing Appointment of Janice I. Sodos as Court Expert July 22, 1991 (Box-folder 5:39)
      - Order – Setting Deadlines for Motions for Unitary Status August 18, 1991 (Box-folder 5:40)
      - Brief of Michigan Education Association in Response to Defendants’ Motions for Declaration of Unitary Status October 15, 1991 (Box-folder 5:41)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee January 1, 1991 – October 31, 1991 (Box-folder 5:42)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos November 25, 1991 (Box-folder 5:43)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee November 1, 1991 – December 31, 1992 (Box-folder 5:44)
      - Order -- Section 21 of the Michigan State School Aid Act 1992 (Box-folder 5:45)
      - Order -- Continuing Appointment of Janice I. Sodos as Court Expert May 10, 1993 (Box-folder 5:46)
      - Restraining Order -- Barbara Whitfield May 13, 1993 (Box-folder 5:47)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee January 1, 1993 – July 31, 1993 (Box-folder 5:48)
      - Order -- Community Education Council Fiscal September 21, 1993 (Box-folder 5:49)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos November 22, 1993 (Box-folder 5:50)
      - Order -- Motions Dismissed December 3, 1993 (Box-folder 5:51)
      - Order – Continuing Appointment of Janice I. Sodos as Court Expert May 26, 1994 (Box-folder 5:52)
      - Supplemental Memo of Eau Claire Regarding Joint Motion Concerning Incentive Grant Payments June 7, 1994 (Box-folder 5:53)
      - Certificate of Service – LuAnn Haldy June 7, 1994 (Box-folder 5:54)
      - Stipulation – Between Defendants Coloma Community Schools, Eau Claire School District and State of Michigan Regarding Social Security and Medicare Reimbursements and Payments for 1992-93 and 1993-94 and Inclusion for 1994-95 Basic Foundation Allowance Purposes June 9, 1994 (Box-folder 5:55)
      - Opinion – Regarding Motion Concerning Incentive Grant Monies June 23, 1994 (Box-folder 5:56)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee August 1, 1993 – November 14, 1994 (Box-folder 5:57)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee November 15, 1994 – March 12, 1995 (Box-folder 6:1)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee March 13, 1995 – August 18, 1995 (Box-folder 6:2)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee August 19, 1995 – October 19, 1995 (Box-folder 6:3)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee November 15, 1994 – October 19, 1995 (Box-folder 6:4)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Janice I. Sodos August 16, 1995-January 26, 1996 (Box-folder 6:5)
      - Order – Continuing Appointment of Janice I. Sodos as Court Expert, February 1, 1996 (Box-folder 6:6)
      - Joint Motion for Tentative Court Approval March 27, 29, 1996 (Box-folder 6:7)
      - Certificate of Service – Timothy P. Gladney March 29, 1996 (Box-folder 6:8)
      - Notice of Hearing March 29, 1996 (Box-folder 6:9)
      - Order – Countryside Charter School April 5, 1996 (Box-folder 6:10)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee October 20, 1995-April 20, 1996 (Box-folder 6:11)
      - Order - Countryside Charter School April 23, 1996 (Box-folder 6:12)
      - Order – Settlement Agreement May 8, 1996 (Box-folder 6:13)
      - Order – Fairness Hearing June 3, 1996 (Box-folder 6:14)
      - Order – Benton Harbor Area School District Parent Input Forms June 6, 1996 (Box-folder 6:15)
      - Opinion Regarding Motion for Approval of Proposed Settlement June 27, 1996 (Box-folder 6:16)
      - Appeals – Notice of Appeal July 26, 1996 (Box-folder 6:17)
      - Order – Michigan Rules of Professional Conduct August 2, 1996 (Box-folder 6:18)
      - Appeals – Notice of Appeal August 6, 1996 (Box-folder 6:19)
      - Appeals – Notice of Appeal August 7, 1996 (Box-folder 6:20)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee April 21, 1996-August 13, 1996 (Box-folder 6:21)
      - Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee October 20, 1995 – August 26, 1996 (Box-folder 6:22)
      - Order – Joint Motion for Approval of Stipulation to Modify May 1, 1981 Remedial Order September 16, 1996 (Box-folder 6:23)
      - Opinion – Modifications to State Funding / May 1, 1981 Remedial Order Approved September 30, 1996 (Box-folder 6:24)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee August 27, 1996-December 31, 1996 (Box-folder 6:25)
      - Court Notices 1996-97 (Box-folder 6:26)
      - Order – Magnet Schools 1996 (Box-folder 6:27)
      - Order - Granting Plaintiffs’ Motion for Substitution of Class Representatives to Appoint Next Friends for Infant Plaintiffs January 29, 1997 (Box-folder 6:28)
      - Order – Granting Petition to Permit Funding of Countryside Charter School April 29, 1997 (Box-folder 6:29)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee January 1, 1997-April 30, 1997 (Box-folder 6:30)
      - Order - Denying Defendants’ Motion for Extension of Time December 3, 1997 (Box-folder 6:31)
      - Order – Plaintiff’s Motion for Consultant Fees Vacated December 16, 1997 (Box-folder 6:32)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee May 1, 1997-December 31, 1997 (Box-folder 6:33)
      - Order – Fees and Expenses, Dr. Michael J. Stolee January 1, 1998-August 12, 1998 (Box-folder 6:34)
      - Order - To Show Cause September 14, 1999 (Box-folder 6:35)
      - Stipulation – Berrien County Intermediate School District October 1, 1999 (Box-folder 6:36)
      - Opinion Re Various Motions October 8, 1999 (Box-folder 6:37)
      - Order – Informal Conference November 10, 1999 (Box-folder 6:38)
      - Order – Educational Options Academy December 28, 1999 (Box-folder 6:39)
      - Appeals – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6:40)
      - Proposed Order - Berrien County Vocational Technology Education Program undated (Box-folder 6:41)
    - Benton Harbor 1980 to 1988
      - Acceptance Forms 1996-97 (Box-folder 7:1)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1982-83 (Box-folder 7:2)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1983-84 (Box-folder 7:3)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1984-85 (Box-folder 7:4)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1985-86 (Box-folder 7:5)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1986-87 (Box-folder 7:6)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1988-89 (Box-folder 7:7)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1989-90 (Box-folder 7:8)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1990-91 (Box-folder 7:9)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1991-92 (Box-folder 7:10)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1992-93 (Box-folder 7:11)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1993-94 (Box-folder 7:12)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1995-96 (Box-folder 7:13)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1996-97 (Box-folder 8:1)
      - Benton Harbor Case, Schedule of 1991-92 Payments 1991-92 (Box-folder 8:2)
      - Benton Harbor High School Report February 8, 1996 (Box-folder 8:3)
      - Case History 1980-1998 (Box-folder 8:4)
      - Correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 8:5)
      - Correspondence 1995-96 (Box-folder 8:6)
      - Countryside Charter School 1996-97 (Box-folder 8:7)
      - Creative Arts Academy 1985-87 (Box-folder 8:8)
      - Expense Advances 1994 (Box-folder 8:9)
      - Financial Report June 30, 1994 (Box-folder 8:10)
      - Financial Report June 30, 1995 (Box-folder 8:11)
      - Financial Report June 30, 1996 (Box-folder 8:12)
      - Financial Report June 30, 1997 (Box-folder 8:13)
      - Incident Reports 1996 (Box-folder 8:14)
      - IRS Notice of Levy on Wages, Salary, and Other Income May 1, 1995 (Box-folder 8:15)
      - A Proposed Evaluation Design for Evaluating the Court’s Desegregation Plan in Benton Harbor December 17, 1986 (Box-folder 8:16)
    - Coloma 1981 to 1999
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1981-82 (Box-folder 9:1)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1982-83 (Box-folder 9:2)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1983-84 (Box-folder 9:3)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1984-85 (Box-folder 9:4)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1985-86 (Box-folder 9:5)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1986-87 (Box-folder 9:6)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1988-89 (Box-folder 9:7)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1989-90 (Box-folder 9:8)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1990-91 (Box-folder 9:9)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1991-92 (Box-folder 9:10)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1992-93 (Box-folder 9:11)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1993-94 (Box-folder 9:12)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1994-95 (Box-folder 9:13)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1995-96 (Box-folder 9:14)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1996-97 (Box-folder 9:15)
      - Admin. Questionnaire 1989 (Box-folder 10:1)
      - Athletic Handbook 1990 (Box-folder 10:2)
      - Bidding 1982 (Box-folder 10:3)
      - Board of Education Meeting May 14, 1990 (Box-folder 10:4)
      - Coloma Education Association 1987-88 (Box-folder 10:5)
      - Correspondence I 1981 (Box-folder 10:6)
      - Correspondence II 1981 (Box-folder 10:7)
      - Correspondence 1982 (Box-folder 10:8)
      - Correspondence 1983 (Box-folder 10:9)
      - Correspondence 1984 (Box-folder 10:10)
      - Correspondence 1985 (Box-folder 10:11)
      - Correspondence 1986 (Box-folder 10:12)
      - Correspondence 1987 (Box-folder 10:13)
      - Correspondence 1988 (Box-folder 10:14)
      - Correspondence 1989 (Box-folder 10:15)
      - Correspondence 1990 (Box-folder 10:16)
      - Correspondence 1991 (Box-folder 10:17)
      - Correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 10:18)
      - Correspondence 1993 (Box-folder 10:19)
      - Correspondence 1994 (Box-folder 10:20)
      - Correspondence 1995 (Box-folder 10:21)
      - Correspondence 1996 (Box-folder 10:22)
      - Correspondence 1997 (Box-folder 10:23)
      - Correspondence 1999 (Box-folder 10:24)
      - Desegregation / Human Relations Training Program undated (Box-folder 10:25)
      - Early Child Program for “at-risk” Children 1988 (Box-folder 10:26)
      - Enrollment Report April 1996 (Box-folder 10:27)
      - Exception / Transfer Requests undated (Box-folder 10:28)
      - Expulsions 1992 (Box-folder 10:29)
      - High School Accreditation 1989 (Box-folder 10:30)
      - Incident Reports 1996 (Box-folder 10:31)
      - Legal Residence for Public School Membership Completed Forms 1997 (Box-folder 11:1)
      - Meeting Notes Regarding Track Coach Resignation 1992 (Box-folder 11:2)
      - On-campus Suspension Center Closing and Remodel 1989-90 (Box-folder 11:3)
      - Proposed Calendar 1991-92 (Box-folder 11:4)
      - Proposed Calendar 1992-93 (Box-folder 11:5)
      - Proposed Calendar 1995-96 (Box-folder 11:6)
      - Proposed Calendar 1997-98 (Box-folder 11:7)
      - Resolution: Coloma Community Schools June 30, 1989 (Box-folder 11:8)
      - Survey to Determine Impact of Attendance Reduction Factor on Resident and Transfer Students October 29, 1991 (Box-folder 11:9)
      - Suspension Report 1984-85 (Box-folder 11:10)
      - Suspension Report 1985-86 (Box-folder 11:11)
      - Suspension Report 1986-87 (Box-folder 11:12)
      - Suspension Report 1987-88 (Box-folder 11:13)
      - Suspension Report 1988-89 (Box-folder 11:14)
      - Suspension Report 1989-90 (Box-folder 11:15)
      - Suspension Report 1990-91 (Box-folder 11:16)
      - Suspension Report 1991-92 (Box-folder 11:17)
      - Suspension Report 1992-93 (Box-folder 11:18)
      - Suspension Report 1993-94 (Box-folder 11:19)
      - Suspension Report 1994-95 (Box-folder 11:20)
      - Suspension Report 1995-96 (Box-folder 11:21)
      - Suspension Report 1996-97 (Box-folder 11:22)
      - Suspension Report 1997-98 (Box-folder 11:23)
      - Teacher Hiring and Reassignment and Affirmative Action Goals for Faculty and Staff September 21, 1981 (Box-folder 11:24)
      - Washington Elementary Staff Concerns 1990 (Box-folder 11:25)
    - Eau Claire 1981 to 1998
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1981-82 (Box-folder 12:1)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1983-84 (Box-folder 12:2)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1984-85 (Box-folder 12:3)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1985-86 (Box-folder 12:4)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1986-87 (Box-folder 12:5)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1988-89 (Box-folder 12:6)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1989-90 (Box-folder 12:7)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1990-91 (Box-folder 12:8)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1991-92 (Box-folder 12:9)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1994-95 (Box-folder 12:10)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1995-96 (Box-folder 12:11)
      - Annual Desegregation Report 1996-97 (Box-folder 12:12)
      - Correspondence 1981 (Box-folder 12:13)
      - Correspondence 1982 (Box-folder 12:14)
      - Correspondence 1983 (Box-folder 12:15)
      - Correspondence 1985 (Box-folder 12:16)
      - Correspondence 1986 (Box-folder 12:17)
      - Correspondence 1987 (Box-folder 12:18)
      - Correspondence 1988 (Box-folder 12:19)
      - Correspondence 1989 (Box-folder 12:20)
      - Correspondence 1990 (Box-folder 12:21)
      - Correspondence 1991 (Box-folder 12:22)
      - Correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 12:23)
      - Correspondence 1993 (Box-folder 12:24)
      - Correspondence 1994 (Box-folder 12:25)
      - Correspondence 1995 (Box-folder 12:26)
      - Correspondence 1996 (Box-folder 12:27)
      - Correspondence 1997 (Box-folder 12:28)
      - Correspondence 1998 (Box-folder 12:29)
      - Enrollment Report April 1996 (Box-folder 12:30)
      - ECHS Academic Probation Policy Proposal February 22, 1995 (Box-folder 12:31)
      - In-School Suspension Program Guidelines 1985 (Box-folder 12:32)
      - Proposed Calendar 1997-98 (Box-folder 12:33)
      - Special Board Meeting May 5, 1994 (Box-folder 12:34)
      - Suspensions 1985-86 (Box-folder 12:35)
      - Suspensions 1986-87 (Box-folder 12:36)
      - Suspensions 1987-88 (Box-folder 12:37)
      - Suspensions 1990-91 (Box-folder 12:38)
      - Teacher Hiring and Reassignment and Affirmative Action Goals for Faculty and Staff 1981 (Box-folder 12:39)
    - Community Education Council 1989 to 1997
      - CEC Appointments April 30, 1997 (Box-folder 13:1)
      - CEC Alternative Education Program 1996-97 (Box-folder 13:2)
      - CEC Budget 1992-97 (Box-folder 13:3)
      - CEC Career Pathway 1997 (Box-folder 13:4)
      - CEC Correspondence 1986, 1989, 1991-97 (Box-folder 13:5)
      - CEC Fairness Response Forms 1996 (Box-folder 13:6)
      - CEC Information Sheets 1996 (Box-folder 13:7)
      - CEC List of Benton Harbor Plaintiffs August 14, 1996 (Box-folder 13:8)
      - CEC Meeting Minutes and Agendas 1994-96 (Box-folder 13:9)
      - CEC Members 1995-96 (Box-folder 13:10)
      - CEC Questionnaire undated (Box-folder 13:11)
      - CEC Time and Effort Logs 1996-97 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Superintendents Council 1981 to 1999
      formerly the Magnet Programs Committee
      - Superintendents Council 1981 (Box-folder 14:1)
      - Superintendents Council 1982 (Box-folder 14:2)
      - Superintendents Council 1983 (Box-folder 14:3)
      - Superintendents Council 1984 (Box-folder 14:4)
      - Superintendents Council 1985 (Box-folder 14:5)
      - Superintendents Council 1986 (Box-folder 14:6)
      - Superintendents Council 1987 (Box-folder 14:7)
      - Superintendents Council 1988 (Box-folder 14:8)
      - Superintendents Council 1989 (Box-folder 14:9)
      - Superintendents Council 1990 (Box-folder 14:10)
      - Superintendents Council 1991 (Box-folder 14:11)
      - Superintendents Council 1992 (Box-folder 14:12)
      - Superintendents Council 1993 (Box-folder 14:13)
      - Superintendents Council 1994 (Box-folder 14:14)
      - Superintendents Council 1995 (Box-folder 14:15)
      - Superintendents Council 1996 (Box-folder 14:16)
      - Superintendents Council 1997 (Box-folder 14:17)
      - Superintendents Council 1998 (Box-folder 14:18)
      - Superintendents Council 1999 (Box-folder 14:19)
    - Michael J. Stolee Correspondence 1981 to 1998
      - Michael J. Stolee from Parents / Residents 1989-98 (Box-folder 15:1)
      - Michael J. Stolee from School Superintendents 1986-87 (Box-folder 15:2)
      - Michael J. Stolee to Attorneys 1989-96 (Box-folder 15:3)
      - Michael J. Stolee to Central Michigan University 1995 (Box-folder 15:4)
      - Michael J. Stolee to Community Education Council 1989-95 (Box-folder 15:5)
      - Michael J. Stolee to Judge Douglas W. Hillman 1981-96 (Box-folder 15:6)
      - Michael J. Stolee to Parents 1984-96 (Box-folder 15:7)
      - Michael J. Stolee to School Superintendents 1981-89 (Box-folder 15:8)
      - Michael J. Stolee to School Superintendents 1990-97 (Box-folder 15:9)
      - Michael J. Stolee Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 15:10)
    - Judge Hillman Correspondence 1981 to 1998
      - Judge Hillman from Parents / Residents 1981, 1996-97 (Box-folder 15:11)
      - Judge Hillman to Attorneys 1995-97 (Box-folder 15:12)
      - Judge Hillman to Community Education Council 1996-97 (Box-folder 15:13)
      - Judge Hillman to Michael J. Stolee 1987, 1994-98 (Box-folder 15:14)
      - Judge Hillman to Parents / Residents 1996-97 (Box-folder 15:15)
      - Judge Hillman to School Superintendents 1984, 1994, 1997-98 (Box-folder 15:16)
      - Folder 17: From Judge Hillman Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 15:17)
      - To Judge Hillman Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 15:18)
    - Janice I. Sodos Correspondence 1988 to 1993
      - Janice I. Sodos 1988 (Box-folder 15:19)
      - Janice I. Sodos 1989 (Box-folder 15:20)
      - Janice I. Sodos 1990 (Box-folder 15:21)
      - Janice I. Sodos 1993 (Box-folder 15:22)
    - Attorney Correspondence 1981 to 1999
      - Dykema Gossett Law Office 1996 (Box-folder 16:1)
      - Frank J. Kelley, Attorney General 1981-85, 1990-97 (Box-folder 16:2)
      - (Hartwig,) Crow and Jones Law Offices 1990-95 (Box-folder 16:3)
      - Herbert Norder and Associates 1981-84 (Box-folder 16:4)
      - Riley and Roumell Attorneys and Counselors at Law 1989-94 (Box-folder 16:5)
      - Riley and Roumell Attorneys and Counselors at Law 1995-99 (Box-folder 16:6)
      - Thrun, Maatsch and Nordberg, P.C. Attorneys and Counselors at Law 1989, 1991, 1995-97 (Box-folder 16:7)
      - Timothy Gladney, Attorney at Law 1995 (Box-folder 16:8)
      - Warner, Norcross, and Judd Attorneys at Law 1989, 1997 (Box-folder 16:9)
      - White, Przybylowicz, Schneider, and Baird, PC. Attorneys at Law 1988, 1991-96 (Box-folder 16:10)
      - Miscellaneous Attorneys undated (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Other Correspondence 1981 to 1997
      - Educational Options Academy Charter 1995-97 (Box-folder 16:12)
      - Michigan Education Association 1988-97 (Box-folder 16:13)
      - Michigan State University 1986-88 (Box-folder 16:14)
      - NAACP 1984-96 (Box-folder 16:15)
      - State of Michigan Department of Education 1981-89 (Box-folder 16:16)
      - State of Michigan Department of Education 1990-97 (Box-folder 16:17)
    - General Michigan Materials 1982 to 1998
      - Attorneys’ Meeting May 10, 1990 (Box-folder 17:1)
      - Calendar – Benton Harbor, Coloma, and Eau Claire School Districts 1988-89 (Box-folder 17:2)
      - Calendar – Benton Harbor, Coloma, and Eau Claire School Districts 1989-90 (Box-folder 17:3)
      - Chapter I Funds 1986-90 (Box-folder 17:4)
      - Handwritten Notes undated (Box-folder 17:5)
      - Inter-district Transfers September 27, 1996 (Box-folder 17:6)
      - Long-Range Planning Committee for Berry, et al v. Benton Harbor, et al 1990-91 (Box-folder 17:7)
      - Magnet Schools 1995-96 (Box-folder 17:8)
      - Memos to Students and Parents of Benton Harbor, Coloma, and Eau Claire Schools 1995 (Box-folder 17:9)
      - News Clippings 1990-98 (Box-folder 17:10)
      - Photo – Jim Turner, Mike, and Judge Hillman undated (Box-folder 17:11)
      - Principal Questionnaires April 26, 1985 (Box-folder 17:12)
      - Public Act 25: The Quality of Education Package, Michigan State Board of Education August 1990 (Box-folder 17:13)
      - Section 27 / 25 Funds 1990 (Box-folder 17:14)
      - Student Attendance Policy November 1990 (Box-folder 17:15)
      - Students’ Rights and Responsibilities in Michigan 1982 (Box-folder 17:16)
  - Minnesota 1972 and 1982
    This sub-series includes Minneapolis from 1972 and 1982.
    - Minneapolis 1972 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Minneapolis News Clippings 1972, 1982 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Mississippi 1985 to 1989
    This sub-series includes Cleveland in 1989; Lawrence County from 1985 and 1987; and Natchez from 1988 to 1989.
    - Cleveland – Fees and Expenses 1989 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - Lawrence County 1985, 1987 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - Natchez 1988-89 (Box-folder 18:5)
    - Natchez Deposition January 25, 1989 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Natchez Desegregation Plan 1989 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Natchez Telephone Deposition May 9, 1989 (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Missouri 1976 to 1998
    This sub-series includes Kansas City from 1976 and 1996 to 1998; and St. Louis from 1977, 1982, and 1984.
    - Kansas City 1976, 1996-98 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - Kansas City News Clippings 1976 (Box-folder 18:10)
    - Saint Louis Desegregation 1977, 1982 (Box-folder 18:11)
    - Saint Louis News Clippings 1977, 1984 (Box-folder 18:12)
  - North Carolina 1976 to 1999
    This sub-series includes Charlotte from 1992-1999; Raleigh from 1976 to 1979; and Rocky Mount from 1990 to 1991.
    - Charlotte 1991-99 (Box-folder 18:13)
    - Charlotte-Mecklenburg Plan January 1992 (Box-folder 18:14)
    - Charlotte News Clippings 1992 (Box-folder 18:15)
    - Recommendations for Pupil Assignment Plan, Charlotte-Mecklenburg Schools October 1993 (Box-folder 18:16)
    - Student Assignment Plan, Charlotte-Mecklenburg Schools March 1992 (Box-folder 18:17)
    - Student Assignment Plan - Five-year plan, Charlotte-Mecklenburg Schools February 1992 (Box-folder 18:18)
    - Raleigh 1976-79 (Box-folder 18:19)
    - Raleigh News Clippings 1977 (Box-folder 18:20)
    - Rocky Mount 1990-91 (Box-folder 18:21)
  - Ohio 1977 to 1981
    This sub-series includes Columbus from 1977 to 1981.
    - Columbus 1977-81 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Pennsylvania 1972 to 1975
    This sub-series includes Philadelphia from 1972 to 1975.
    - Philadelphia 1972-75 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - South Carolina 1994
    This sub-series includes Florence for 1994.
    - Florence 1994 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Tennessee 1972 to 2001